<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Erlich Bachman</title>
    <link>https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Erlich Bachman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 16:59:13 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooli’s Hot New Hardware</title>
      <link>https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 16:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/third/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Note: This article originally appeared in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.coderag.com/hoolis-hot-new-hardware/&#34;&gt;CodeRag&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Hooli acquired Endframe, no one could wait to see what the tech giant would do with the revolutionary, middle-out compression technology. The wait is over: In a savvy pivot, Hooli took the software and created their newest hardware: the Hooli/Endframe Box. While initially conceived as a consumer-facing platform, the Endframe technology has been repurposed to “make the world a better place through secure, high-capacity enterprise data storage servers utilizing middle-out compression technology.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Insanely simple and beautifully crafted, the hardware backs up large amounts of data at a fraction of what it used to cost, so it’s no surprise that enterprise top dog Maleant Data System Solutions jumped at the chance to make a multi-year deal for the product. At a press conference announcing the blockbuster deal, CEO Calvin Greene stated, “The Hooli/Endframe Box is a welcome integration with our banking and medical system clients, who need to process large amounts of secure data at an accelerated pace.” Hooli’s Gavin Belson quipped that the world “always needs more money and doctors.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hardware features a Dual Intel Haswell 2.6 Ghz processor, NVIDIA Tesla K80, Lightnight Eco Gen II SanDisk (800 TB, no less) and two 4TB Seagate hard drives. Matched with Endframe’s middle out algorithm, there’s a reason Maleant promises a 200 percent ROI to any client who elects to incorporate the Hooli/Endframe Box into their service deal with Maleant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two companies flirted with multiple deal options before sealing the deal on a white label agreement, and becoming the power couple of enterprise data storage. Hooli could sell upgraded versions of these boxes to Maleant indefinitely, and Maleant’s penetration in the enterprise market ensures high demand for more Hooli/Endframe Boxes as long as Hooli can keep making them. Hundreds of millions of dollars could follow for Hooli’s enterprise sales division. With these two joining to sell storage solutions, no one will be able to touch their profits—or their data.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gavin Belson</title>
      <link>https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 15:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Note: This article originally appeared in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.coderag.com/10-facts-you-didnt-know-about-gavin-belson/&#34;&gt;CodeRag&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gavin Belson’s name has long been synonymous with innovation—but beyond his work at Hooli, do we even know the man behind the rampant success? In a Code/Rag exclusive, Belson revealed to us 10 things about himself that aren’t common knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He’s a nature fanatic! “It’s important to me that Hooli has an effective recycling program, and a personal passion of mine is donating to elephant sanctuaries. In fact, I’ve recently spearheaded the creation of Hooli’s newest charity: the Hooli Elephant Wildlife Trust.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He likes to go analog! His company may have been founded on email, but Belson has a soft spot for the written word. “There’s something nostalgic about receiving a letter—it’s a message from the past.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He’s an honorary shaman! “I studied at the Institute of Spiritual Therapy and Vision Quests, where I was honored with the title of shaman. The Institute has fundamentally furthered my understanding of the world and its capacity for greatness.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;His favorite pizza topping is pepperoni! “Uncured, preferably, with some aged parmesan.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He drives a Tesla! “Black. I try not to bee too conspicuous. And of course, the benefit to the environment is incomparable.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;His health is important to him! “I eat at least one piece of unprocessed fruit a day.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He has bad habits too! “I never reboot my laptop. I know it’s bad, but I’m always in a hurry.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He doesn’t have a Nobel Peace Prize…yet! “It’s a common misconception, especially with the amount of charity work I do with Hooli, and sometimes people associate my status as a shaman with working towards world peace, which of course is something I’m striving for.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He’s loyal to his barber! “I’ve been going to the same barber for years—he was based in Palo Alto, but I’ve convinced him to move to the South Bay.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;He really, really loves animals! “I would say I’m a cat person. And a dog person. I’m an animal person, and I don’t just mean that human beings are animals. Did you know the African bush elephant is still an endangered species? Programs like the Hooli Elephant Wildlife Trust won’t save them immediately, but it’s a start.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belson Back on Top</title>
      <link>https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 16:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shenoybr.github.io/hugo-goa-demo/blog/second/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Note: This post originally appeared in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.coderag.com/belson-back-on-top-hoolis-ceo-focusing-on-the-bottom-line/&#34;&gt;CodeRag&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gavin Belson’s brilliant leadership is unstoppable. While allegedly taking a personal hiatus from day-to-day operations at Hooli, Belson couldn’t resist brokering a blockbuster deal between Hooli and Maleant Data Systems, deploying Hooli’s innovative new Hooli/Endframe Box. The multi-year deal brings handsome margins for Hooli and can easily be a template to apply across the entire Fortune 1000. An inside source tells me that, no surprise, the board was no longer satisfied to let Belson fade into the background. Hat in hand, they begged Belson to come back to the helm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been barely two months since Belson announced he would be taking a leave from his leadership role in order to focus on spiritual wellness and family. What drove Belson to this decision remains unclear. Was it additional fallout from the Hooli-Search scandal we broke at this very blog? Or perhaps his cutthroat methods in managing Hooli-Search results indicate a demand across the board for higher standards, and as such, Belson could not tolerate the sloppy security upgrades we also reported on. In any case, it seems the company’s electrical issues are resolved, and with it, any spirituality Belson felt the need to examine. The company’s Chief Innovation Officer has returned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Belson, who is single, has had a slew of successes at Hooli this past year. When he announced the dissolution of the Nucleus project, his bravery was rewarded as Hooli stock jumped 7 percent. The cost savings was compounded when Belson pulled the trigger on company-wide layoffs, and the hole left by Nucleus was quickly filled when he acquired middle-out company Endframe. Endframe’s tech has long dominated the middle-out space, and it’s no surprise that the Hooli/Endframe relationship has combined Hooli’s resources and innovation with Endframe’s impressive tech to create something obscenely profitable: the Hooli/Endframe Box.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With Belson back on top at Hooli, shareholders can breathe a sigh of relief. While Belson’s career is certainly not without drama, his shrewd business sense and innovative technological accomplishments are what’s shaped Hooli into the company it is today. Without Gavin Belson, there is no Hooli. And without Hooli, where would any of us be?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>